dogasaur.com 2009-10-12

# Privacy Policy - Dogasaur

## Privacy Policy

### Information Collection and Use

This privacy policy explains how we collect, use, and disclose (under certain conditions) your personal information, and explains the steps we have taken to secure your personal information. This also explains your options regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. By visiting Dogasaur.com, you accept the practices described in this policy.

We may partner with other companies to offer you additional products or services. If you sign up for any of these additional products or services, we will share your name and other personal information that is necessary for these other companies to provide the products or services you have signed up for. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices on any web site to which Dogasaur.com links or that links to Dogasaur.com.

When you register to become a member of Dogasaur.com, we collect your name, email address and optionally your hometown, state and country. When you register your dog we collect the information you want to share about that canine such as name, age, likes, dislikes, sex, etc. Your name and email will never be shared, rented, bartered or sold with other users or third-party companies. All information entered about your dog(s) will only be used by Dogasaur.com to display on the site and will never be shared, rented, bartered, sold or exchanged. The website, however, is accessible by anyone with an internet connection and a web browser, which means that any words and photos you post can be copied by any other internet user. That is the nature of the internet and though we discourage anyone from abusing that option, it is something that must be noted.

Your name and email will never be shared with anyone in any way. If you chose to enter your hometown, state or country, that information will be displayed in any of your dog's web pages on the site, but the dog’s page does not share any other personal information or allow access to it.

The biographical information you enter about your dog(s) is instantly available to all other users of the site. Dogasaur.com does not claim rights for the pictures uploaded or the text information you add to the site. Please note, however, that Dogasaur.com is a public site and thus all photos and information you provide are available to anyone with internet access. Due to the nature of the internet you should never post a photo or fact that you do not now or ever want someone else to have access to.

**Cookies.** Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored as text files by your Internet browser on your computer's hard drive. Most Internet browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse cookies from websites or to remove cookies from your hard drive, but if you do, you will not be able to access or use portions of this Dogasaur.com. This Site's cookies do not infiltrate a user's hard drive to gather a user's confidential information.

**Web Beacons.** Web beacons assist in delivering cookies and help us determine whether a web page on Dogasaur.com has been viewed and, if so, how many times.

Third Party Cookies and Web Beacons. We may use third-party advertising companies to help us tailor site content to users or to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and web beacons to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and web beacons is not linked to any personal information collected by us.

**Log Files.** The Dogasaur.com server automatically recognizes the Internet URL from which you access this Site. We may also log your Internet protocol (“IP”) address, Internet service provider, and date/time stamp for system administration, order verification, internal marketing, and system troubleshooting purposes.

**Age.** We respect children's privacy. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under age 13. By using Dogasaur.com, you have represented that you are either 13 years of age or using Dogasaur.com with the supervision of a parent or guardian. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information to us, and rely on a parent or guardian to assist you.

**Internal Use.** We use your personal information to process your order, communicate with you and provide you with customer service. We may internally use your personal information to improve our website’s content and layout, to improve our outreach and marketing efforts (including marketing our services and products to you), and to determine general marketplace information about visitors to this Site.

**Communications with You.** We will use your personal information to communicate with you about our site, your request for information and your orders and deliveries. Also, we may send you a confirmation email when you register with us. We may send you a service-related announcement when it is necessary. If you submit your email address, we use it to deliver information to you.

**External Use.** We do not sell, rent, trade, license or otherwise disclose your specific personal information or financial information to anyone, except that: (a) we sometimes use others to perform specific functions on our behalf, and we may disclose information to help them to perform their service; (b) if you use your credit card to buy products or pay fees, we provide your credit card number (which will be encrypted) to financial-services corporations such as credit-card processors and issuers; (c) we may disclose information in response to requests from law-enforcement officials conducting investigations pursuant to subpoenas, court orders or if we are otherwise required to disclose such information by law; (d) we will release personal information where disclosure is necessary to protect our legal rights, enforce our Terms of Service or other agreements, or to protect ourselves or others; (e) if we acquire or merge with or are acquired by another company or if we dispose of some or all of our assets, your personal information may be disclosed to another company, but that disclosure will be subject to the Privacy Policy in effect; (f) we may share non-personal information with third parties such as advertising partners.

### UNSUBSCRIBE/OPT OUT/CORRECTIONS

Upon your request, we will (a) correct or update your personal information; (b) stop sending emits to your email address; and/or (c) disable your account to prevent any future purchases through that account. You can make these requests at the customer information section of this Site or by telephoning, or emailing your request to unsubscribe at Dogasaur.com. Please do not email your credit-card number.

### UPDATES

We will post any changes or updates to this Policy on Dogasaur.com. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time. If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy, please contact us at info at Dogasaur.com.

### YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to:

Online Privacy Coordinator  
Dogasaur.com
